I really need to [get cracking with] this report if I want to finish it on time.
-- 如果我想按時完成這份報告，我真的需要[開始]研究它。
After the party, we [mopped up] the spilled drinks and cleaned the kitchen.
-- 聚會結束後，我們[擦掉]了溢出的飲料並打掃了廚房。
Your presentation was great, but you might want to [tone] it [down] a bit for the next audience. It's quite a sensitive topic for some people.
-- 你的演講很棒，但你下次可能要[溫和]一點。 對某些人來說這是一個相當敏感的話題。
I'm [having] some friends [over] for dinner tonight.
-- 今晚我[請]一些朋友[過來]吃晚餐。
After a long day at work, I like to spend some time [winding down] before going to bed.
-- 經過一整天的工作後，我喜歡在睡覺前花一些時間[放鬆]。
The car behind us was [hooting], so my dad [sped up] to get out of the way. As soon as we [moved over], the other car [flew past] us and [sped away].
-- 我們後面的車[鳴笛]，所以我爸爸[加速]讓路。 我們一[往旁邊靠]，另一輛車就[飛過]我們並[疾馳而去]。
After washing the dishes, please [put] them [away] in the cabinet.
-- 洗完碗盤後，請把它們[收]進櫃子裡。
The billboard had been up for months, but it was finally [taken down] last week.
-- 該廣告看板已經豎立了幾個月，但上週終於被[拆除]。
I accidentally [threw away] the page with all my passwords.
-- 我不小心[扔掉了]包含我所有密碼的紙張。
Can you help me [pick up] the toys that are [scattered] around the living room?
-- 你能幫我[撿起]客廳裡[散落]的玩具嗎？